Excuse Me,
Are You
Yeah, Really
Mind-Sharing Up
Um, Yeah,
We Met
There We
Go, There
What Was
Your First
She'S Tall.
She Is
Tall.
Yeah.
What Would
You Say?
What Was
Your First
She'S Also
Tall.
She'S Tall.
Okay.
So, How
Long You
We'Re Married.
How Long?
Six Years.
Six Years?
Six Years
And What'S
Um, I
Don'T Know,
Yeah?
Okay, What
Would You
Um, He'S
Always So
That'S Nice.
And How
Did You
We Drove
Three Hours
Oh, Okay.
We Ran
From A
Ranch?
Yeah.
Oh, Nice.
That'S Amazing.
And How
Old Is
Three Years
Old?
Four Years
Okay, Perfect.
Okay.
If You
Guys Have
What Would
You Say?
The Little
Things.
Do The
Little Things.
And Make
A Little
Oh, Okay.
Yeah.
If You
Can Cook
Nice.
Okay.
And If
You Guys
Yeah.
My Name
Is Angela
Okay.
I'M John.
I'M An
Engineer.
Okay.
Perfect.