Are you guys a couple?
Yes.
Yeah, would you mind sharing a picture of you guys first man?
What happened?
We met online.
Yeah.
And then...
Well, the rest is coming straight.
Oh, nice.
We lived multiple states away.
Okay.
Yeah.
And how long you guys dated, like long distance and then the first man?
We dated for...
Six months?
Probably.
Yeah, six months.
Six months?
Yeah.
And then I moved to South Carolina.
Which is where he was living.
Oh, yeah.
And then...
And then married for a while, four years?
Three years.
Three years?
Oh, nice.
Okay.
And what was your first impression of her?
Absolutely gorgeous.
Oh, there you go.
What were you say?
Yes.
She was very good looking, very, very sweet.
What are the nicest, most genuine humans I've ever met?
Nice.
And what's the story of them?
Like, how did you find them?
So, this is our girl that we got first.
This is Aspen.
Yeah.
Just decided we wanted a dog.
I've always wanted a golden retriever.
Okay.
And so, we found a breeder, my cousins, and all of us,
bred golden retrievers.
So, we got her.
And then this guy, we just got, actually from Goldberg and Rescue.
We rescued him in November this last year.
Oh, nice.
That's great.
Okay.
If somebody is getting into a relationship today, what advice would he guys have to give to the...
Communications, import?
Yes.
Okay.
Communication.
What you want.
And...
What?
Yeah.
Okay.
And if you guys are open sharing your name and what do you do for a living?
My name is Kinsy Aminers.
Oh, my name is Riley and I'm an engineer.
Oh, that's great.
Alright guys, thank you so much.
Have a great day.