Excuse me, are you guys a couple?
Yeah, really mind-sharing up a story on how you guys first met?
Um, yeah, we met in college at a frapp party.
There we go, there we go.
What was your first impression of her?
She's tall.
She is tall.
Yeah.
What would you say?
What was your first impression of?
She's also tall.
She's tall.
Okay.
So, how long you guys have been in relationship for?
We're married.
How long?
Six years.
Six years?
Six years and what's your favorite thing about her?
Um, I don't know, she's just had a lot of love in her.
Yeah?
Okay, what would you say?
Um, he's always so positive and so fine.
That's nice.
And how did you get her?
We drove three hours to Bowie Texas and we found her.
Oh, okay.
We ran from a ranch.
We ran from a ranch, yeah.
From a ranch?
Yeah.
Oh, nice. That's amazing.
And how old is she?
Three years old?
Four years old?
Okay, perfect.
Okay.
If you guys have to give our relationship advice for somebody who is just getting into one,
what would you say?
The little things.
Do the little things.
And make a little thing spun and then the whole relationship spun.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
If you can cook and clean with them, then it's the personal thing that people love.
Nice.
Okay.
And if you guys are open sharing your name and what do you do for 11?
Yeah.
My name is Angela and I'm a recruiter.
Okay.
I'm John.
I'm an engineer.
Okay.
Perfect.